"The little brother killed his big brother."
"الأخ الصغير قتل أخاه الكبير."
That was just a dream. Our swim, the overnight stay,
كان مجرد حلم. سباحتنا، ومبيتنا،
everything we shared that morning, all of that was just a dream!
كل ما شاركناه في ذلك الصباح، كان مجرد حلم!
We were really together in Montanesa.
لقد كنا حقا معا في مونتانيسا.
That's all it'll ever be.
هذا كل ما سيكون عليه الأمر.
Are you cutting me out of your life
هل تقطعني من حياتك؟
just to try to make up for your past with your brother?
فقط لمحاولة التعويض عن ماضيك مع أخيك؟
It's wrong that I keep forgetting Matmat.
من الخطأ أن أنسى مطمت باستمرار.
It was a mistake that I ever entertained having you in my life.
لقد كان من الخطأ أن أستمتع بوجودك في حياتي.
Stop playing hostage and victim to your family.
توقف عن لعب دور الرهينة والضحية لعائلتك.
I know that.
وأنا أعلم ذلك.
But that doesn't mean my conscience is clear.
ولكن هذا لا يعني أن ضميري مرتاح.
Mia, let's stop this.
ميا، دعونا نوقف هذا.
This is where it ends for us.
وهنا ينتهي الأمر بالنسبة لنا.
Miss Mia!
آنسة ميا!
What's really my purpose in life?
ما هو هدفي الحقيقي في الحياة؟
I'm giving security guard vibes here.
أنا أعطي اهتزازات حارس الأمن هنا.
- Madeth, you need to do this.
- ماديث، عليك أن تفعل هذا.
We still haven't spoken to Mia!
لم نتحدث مع ميا بعد!
But boss,
ولكن يا رئيس،
could she at least let me in the house?
هل يمكنها على الأقل أن تسمح لي بالدخول إلى المنزل؟
Just keep knocking, she can't not open the door.
فقط استمر بالطرق، فهي لا تستطيع أن تفتح الباب.
-
-
- Miss Mia! You can't leave her.
- آنسة ميا! لا يمكنكِ تركها.
Because it's her birthday tomorrow.
لأنه عيد ميلادها غدا.
Huh?
هاه؟
Then why am I the one here?
ثم لماذا أنا هنا؟
I should be the one fixing the surprises.
يجب أن أكون الشخص الذي يصلح المفاجآت.
The confetti, cake,
الحلويات، الكعكة،
spring rolls!
لفائف الربيع!
Madeth, you don't understand.
ماديث، أنت لا تفهم.
Mia can't be alone because…
ميا لا تستطيع أن تكون وحيدة لأن...
when it's your birthday, you remember being born, right?
عندما يكون عيد ميلادك، تتذكر أنك ولدت، أليس كذلك؟
Of course, it's my birthday.
بالطبع، إنه عيد ميلادي.
I'm not finished yet!
لم أنتهي بعد!
So you remember, your birth,
لذا تتذكر ميلادك،
- you remember, your mother.
- هل تتذكر والدتك؟
Ahh.
آه.
And Miss Mia shouldn't remember her mom?
ولا ينبغي للسيدة ميا أن تتذكر أمها؟
Oh, thank you!
أوه، شكرا لك!
She'll have a hard time, so make sure she's okay.
سوف تواجه وقتًا عصيبًا، لذا تأكد من أنها بخير.
And your planned surprises?
وما هي المفاجآت التي خططت لها؟
Just do them there.
فقط افعلها هناك.
Huh?
هاه؟
How?
كيف؟
Boss…
رئيس…
Why do I have to do it all? What are you going to do?
لماذا عليّ أن أفعل كل هذا؟ ماذا ستفعل؟
Of course, I'll do something. I won't just do nothing!
بالطبع سأفعل شيئًا. لن أكتفي بالصمت!
You sure, boss?
هل أنت متأكد يا رئيس؟
I might end up working harder than you.
ربما سأعمل بجهد أكبر منك.
Madeth, you know I always give Mia my best effort, right?
ماديث، أنت تعرف أنني دائمًا أبذل قصارى جهدي لميا، أليس كذلك؟
So go ahead, I still have things to do here.
إذن اذهب، لا يزال لدي أشياء لأفعلها هنا.
Boss!
رئيس!
Miss Mia!
آنسة ميا!
Miss Mia?
آنسة ميا؟
Ma, let's go!
أماه، هيا بنا!
Wait, wait a second!
انتظر، انتظر ثانية!
I'm still stretching out my knees.
لا أزال أمد ركبتي.
Ma, are you sure you can still go to work?
أمي، هل أنت متأكدة من أنك لا تزالين قادرة على الذهاب إلى العمل؟
Yes, but you go to your Aunt Sugar instead.
نعم، ولكن عليك أن تذهب إلى عمتك شوغر بدلا من ذلك.
Pick up the mangoes I ordered, okay?
التقط المانجو التي طلبتها، حسنًا؟
- Okay? Okay, I'll get them.
- حسنًا؟ حسنًا، سأحضرهم.
Uh, do you need company? Do you need help?
هل تحتاج إلى رفقة؟ هل تحتاج إلى مساعدة؟
- No, I can manage. Yes, she does.
لا، أستطيع. نعم، تستطيع.
Ma, how many kilos of mangoes did you order?
أمي كم كيلو مانجو طلبتي؟
Two kilos.
كيلوغرامين.
Oh, help her carry those, okay?
أوه، ساعدها في حمل تلك الأشياء، حسنًا؟
Since he's been working out.
منذ أن بدأ العمل.
Ma, I'm sure I can carry two kilos of mangoes.
أمي، أنا متأكدة من أنني أستطيع حمل كيلوغرامين من المانجو.
No, make it ten kilos. I'll sell some at the hospital.
لا، خلّيها عشرة كيلو. هبيعها في المستشفى.
Her mangoes are sweet.
مانجوها حلوة.
Oh, my knees. And also,
أوه، ركبتي. وأيضًا،
you drive, okay?
أنت تقود، حسنًا؟
- Alright, Ma. - Dear, you'll get tired.
- حسنًا يا أمي. - عزيزتي، سوف تتعبين.
Let him drive.
دعوه يقود.
Ma, it looks like your knees are fine--
أماه، يبدو أن ركبتيك بخير--
No, they still hurt!
لا، لا زالوا يؤلمون!
- Look, they still hurt. You were just pushing me…
انظر، ما زالوا يؤلمون. كنتَ تدفعني فقط...
Okay, Ma, we'll go ahead. Take care of your knees.
حسنًا يا أمي، لنبدأ. اعتني بركبتيك.
Yes, Vincent, take care of her, okay?
نعم، فينسنت، اعتني بها، حسنًا؟
- Got it! - Okay!
- فهمت! - حسنًا!
Ouch…
آخ…
Olivia?
أوليفيا؟
What's that for?
ما هذا؟
For Matmat.
لماتمات.
I heard he's into dinosaurs.
سمعت أنه مهتم بالديناصورات.
I'll take it to him, it might help.
سأأخذه إليه، قد يساعد.
You even meddle with non-patients?
هل تتدخل حتى مع غير المرضى؟
Come on Eden,
تعال يا عدن
you turn every act of kindness into a problem.
أنت تحول كل عمل طيب إلى مشكلة.
Are you really that pessimistic about life?
هل أنت حقا متشائم بشأن الحياة؟
Excuse me, Miss Olivia.
عذرا، آنسة أوليفيا.
I need help with a patient.
أحتاج إلى مساعدة مع مريض.
M-mama…
م-أمي…
M-mama dinosaur!
أم الديناصور!
Hello, Matmat!
مرحباً، مطمت!
May I come in?
هل يمكنني الدخول؟
M-mama dinosaur!
أم الديناصور!
M-mama
انا امي
dinosaur!
ديناصور!
M-mama…
م-أمي…
Did you see that, Nurse Eden?
هل رأيت ذلك يا ممرضة إيدن؟
She's Mama Dinosaur.
إنها أم الديناصور.
But,
لكن،
did you know there are other dinosaurs?
هل تعلم أن هناك ديناصورات أخرى؟
Tyrannosaurus rex, Spinosaurus,
تيرانوصور ريكس، سبينوصور،
Giganotosaurus.
جيجانوتوصور.
It all depends on,
كل هذا يعتمد على،
when they were born.
عندما ولدوا.
Is there a dinosaur that can fly?
هل يوجد ديناصور يستطيع الطيران؟
Pterodactyl.
البتروداكتيل.
Looks like a dinosaur, but it's not.
يبدو وكأنه ديناصور، لكنه ليس كذلك.
That's what the book says.
هذا ما يقوله الكتاب.
Oh, why aren't they dinosaurs?
أوه، لماذا لا يكونون ديناصورات؟
T-They're related to dinosaurs.
ت-إنهم مرتبطون بالديناصورات.
Like cousins.
مثل أبناء العم.
Their bodies are just different.
أجسادهم مختلفة فقط.
Hmm. I see.
هممم. أرى.
So, animals have families too, right?
إذن، الحيوانات لديها عائلات أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Like you and Patpat, you're family.
مثلك ومثل باتبات، أنت عائلة.
You're so nice, M-Mama Dinosaur.
أنت لطيفة جدًا، يا أم الديناصور.
Is Mama Dinosaur nice?
هل ماما الديناصور لطيفة؟
Yes, she's nice.
نعم إنها لطيفة.
Like your mama?
مثل أمك؟
My mama is nice.
أمي لطيفة.
But she's not always to my little brother.
لكنها لا تكون كذلك دائمًا مع أخي الصغير.
She's always nice to Matmat but,
إنها لطيفة دائمًا مع ماتمات، لكن،
s-sometimes not to Patpat.
س-أحيانًا لا يصل إلى Patpat.
Drink some soup.
اشرب بعض الحساء.
There's ginger.
هناك الزنجبيل.
It's good for your immune system.
إنه جيد لجهاز المناعة لديك.
This caldereta's just the right spice,
هذه الكالدريتا هي التوابل المثالية،
to wake up your appetite.
لإيقاظ شهيتك.
Don't like malunggay? You've got bitter ground.
ألا تحبّ المالونغاي؟ لديك أرضٌ مُرّة.
You need vegetables.
تحتاج إلى الخضروات.
If you don't want meat, there's fish here.
إذا كنت لا تريد اللحوم، هناك الأسماك هنا.
I'm sorry for troubling you.
أنا آسف لإزعاجك.
You don't need to worry about me too.
لا داعي للقلق عليّ أيضاً.
Honestly, I'm thinking…
بصراحة أنا أفكر...
maybe I should've just thrown you out.
ربما كان ينبغي لي أن أطردك.
What?
ماذا؟
My daughter hasn't admitted her feelings, and you already rejected her.
ابنتي لم تعترف بمشاعرها، وأنت رفضتها بالفعل.
If I were some other mother,
لو كنت أمًا أخرى،
you'd probably be getting yelled at and cursed right now.
من المحتمل أن يتم الصراخ عليك ولعنك الآن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
But I'm not that kind of mother.
ولكنني لست من هذا النوع من الأمهات.
My conscience wouldn't let me do that.
ضميري لن يسمح لي بفعل ذلك.
And I can't stand seeing people around me go hungry.
ولا أستطيع أن أتحمل رؤية الناس من حولي جائعين.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
And again, I'm really sorry.
ومرة أخرى، أنا آسف حقا.
I'll accept your apology
سأقبل اعتذارك
once you eat and regain your strength.
بمجرد أن تأكل وتستعيد قوتك.
If it's okay with you, I'll take Matmat home
إذا كان الأمر مناسبًا لك، فسوف آخذ ماتمات إلى المنزل
so you can focus on yourself.
لكي تتمكن من التركيز على نفسك.
Then when you're feeling okay, you two can talk.
ثم عندما تشعران أنكما بخير، يمكنكم التحدث.
Why are you being so kind to us?
لماذا أنت لطيف معنا هكذا؟
Whatever you went through before,
مهما مررت به من قبل،
is just part of who you are now.
هو مجرد جزء من شخصيتك الآن.
And from what I see,
ومن ما أرى،
you're such a good kid, Patrick.
أنت طفل جيد جدًا، باتريك.
Because of that kindness,
بسبب هذا اللطف،
I'd be glad to have you as a son in my next life.
سوف أكون سعيدًا أن أجعلك ابنًا لي في حياتي القادمة.
Eat up.
تناول الطعام.
I don't want a next life.
لا أريد حياة أخرى.
Don't you have to work? You'll just get dirty here.
ألا يجب عليك العمل؟ ستتسخ هنا.
No worries!
لا شكر على واجب!
I just have client calls today.
لدي مكالمات عملاء اليوم فقط.
Oh, so you're just sitting around all day.
أوه، لذلك أنت فقط تجلس طوال اليوم.
Yes!
نعم!
But those calls were important, okay?
لكن تلك المكالمات كانت مهمة، أليس كذلك؟
Plus, I am guiding my publishing staff.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، أقوم بتوجيه موظفي النشر الخاص بي.
And we're also preparing for her birthday.
ونحن نستعد أيضًا لعيد ميلادها.
Her birthday?
عيد ميلادها؟
Yes, tomorrow.
نعم غدا.
I need it to be special, for my favorite writer in the world.
أريدها أن تكون خاصة، لكاتبي المفضل في العالم.
Is Mia the only writer in your company?
هل ميا هي الكاتبة الوحيدة في شركتك؟
No, we've got plenty.
لا، لدينا الكثير.
Why'd you ask?
لماذا سألت؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Gemma!
جيما!
Auntie!
عمة!
Good morning! I'm here pick up Mama's order.
صباح الخير! أنا هنا لأستلم طلب ماما.
Oh, right! I forgot!
أوه، صحيح! لقد نسيت!
Can you wait?
أيمكنك الانتظار؟
I had so many customers, so I haven't packed it yet.
لقد كان لدي الكثير من العملاء، لذلك لم أقم بتعبئتها بعد.
Maybe your friend can help out while I sort it?
ربما يمكن لصديقك أن يساعد بينما أقوم بحل هذه المشكلة؟
Sure, auntie! I mean, mom. Wait, no!
بالتأكيد يا عمتي! أقصد يا أمي. لحظة، لا!
But sure, whatever you need!
ولكن بالتأكيد، كل ما تحتاجه!
Apples for you and for you!
التفاح لك ولك!
This apple will change your lives.
هذه التفاحة سوف تغير حياتك
How many kilos?
كم كيلو؟
- Just one. - Okay, sure.
- واحدة فقط. - حسنًا، بالتأكيد.
Auntie, I'll take the mangoes.
عمتي، سوف آخذ المانجو.
Actually, I already prepared them earlier.
في الواقع، لقد قمت بإعدادهم مسبقًا.
Your mother just said you'd be bringing a young man!
لقد قالت والدتك للتو أنك ستحضر شابًا!
Auntie, don't be too loud.
عمتي، لا تكوني عالية الصوت جدًا.
I'll report back to her that this one's approved.
سأبلغها بأن هذا الأمر تمت الموافقة عليه.
Ma'am, here's a thousand. Change please!
سيدتي، إليكِ ألفًا. غيّريها من فضلكِ!
Come on! Just call me auntie.
هيا! فقط ناديني عمتي.
Sure, auntie!
بالتأكيد يا عمتي!
- Auntie, I'll get going. - Alright, sure.
- عمتي، سأذهب. - حسنًا، بالتأكيد.
Vincent, I'm going.
فينسنت، أنا ذاهب.
Oh, wait!
أوه، انتظر!
Take these. You can snack on them later at the hospital.
تناول هذه. يمكنك تناولها لاحقًا في المستشفى.
Gemma,
جيما،
I'd say you're already sweeter than that orange.
أود أن أقول أنك بالفعل أحلى من تلك البرتقالة.
Auntie, I'll walk Gemma over to her car.
عمتي، سأرافق جيما إلى سيارتها.
- Go on. - I'll be back right away.
-استمر. - سأعود على الفور.
Thank you, auntie.
شكرا لك عمتي.
Hey, don't just touch the fruits! Buy them!
مهلا، لا تلمس الفاكهة فقط! اشترها!
Matmat, does your new friend have a name yet?
مطمت، هل صديقك الجديد لديه اسم حتى الآن؟
Why not call her "Mama Joy"?
لماذا لا نسميها "ماما جوي"؟
"Mama Joy"?
"ماما جوي"؟
Why "Mama Joy"?
لماذا "ماما جوي"؟
No reason. I just thought of it.
لا يوجد سبب. لقد فكرت في الأمر فقط.
You said she was like your dinosaur's mama.
لقد قلت أنها كانت مثل أم الديناصور الخاص بك.
Is "Mama Joy" a nice name?
هل "ماما جوي" اسم جميل؟
Sounds like an old lady's name, Miss Li.
يبدو مثل اسم سيدة عجوز، الآنسة لي.
Look, Matmat's smiling now.
انظر، ماتمات يبتسم الآن.
He even chatted with Nurse Eden.
حتى أنه تحدث مع الممرضة إيدن.
Seems like he's okay.
يبدو أنه بخير.
Does that mean you're ready to go home too?
هل هذا يعني أنك مستعد للعودة إلى المنزل أيضًا؟
Remember what we tell our patients?
هل تتذكر ما نقوله لمرضانا؟
If we want a happy environment,
إذا أردنا بيئة سعيدة،
we need to start with ourselves.
علينا أن نبدأ بأنفسنا.
Happiness begins with you.
السعادة تبدأ منك .
Patrick…
باتريك…
Think about your own happiness too.
فكر في سعادتك أيضًا.
So you can share it with Matmat.
حتى تتمكن من مشاركتها مع Matmat.
It's okay to put yourself first some times.
لا بأس من وضع نفسك في المقام الأول في بعض الأحيان.
That's not being selfish.
هذا ليس أنانية.
Can I ask you a favor?
هل يمكنني أن أطلب منك معروفا؟
Wow, boss. You seem so exhausted.
يا رئيس، يبدو أنك مرهق جدًا.
I didn't just man the store, I carried fruit boxes too.
لم أكن أتولى إدارة المتجر فحسب، بل كنت أحمل صناديق الفاكهة أيضًا.
It's your own fault, Boss V.
إنه خطؤك الخاص، يا رئيس V.
You're always trying to show off.
أنت تحاول دائمًا التباهي.
By the way, Boss V.,
بالمناسبة، الرئيس V.
- Gemma texted. - Hmm?
- أرسلت جيما رسالة نصية. - همم؟
- And? - She's asking how you're doing.
- و؟ - إنها تسألك كيف حالك.
She asked if you were late to your client calls.
سألتك إذا كنت متأخرًا في الرد على مكالمات عملائك.
So she's concerned?
فهل هي قلقة؟
She didn't put a smiley or heart emoji.
لم تضع رمزًا مبتسمًا أو قلبًا.
The message seemed neutral, so I'm not sure.
تبدو الرسالة محايدة، لذا لست متأكدًا.
She's definitely concerned!
إنها قلقة بالتأكيد!
You wouldn't ask if you don't care, right?
لن تسأل إذا لم تكن مهتمًا، أليس كذلك؟
Success!
نجاح!
Success? You call that a success? That's all you achieved today!
نجاح؟ أتسميه نجاحاً؟ هذا كل ما حققته اليوم!
I accomplished more things than you today!
لقد أنجزت أشياء أكثر منك اليوم!
I reserved a restaurant.
لقد حجزت مطعمًا.
I ordered a cake as black as Miss Mia's soul.
لقد طلبت كعكة سوداء مثل روح الآنسة ميا.
And Mia? Where's Mia?
وميا؟ أين ميا؟
Dude, she's at home.
يا رجل، إنها في المنزل.
I told you not to leave Mia alone.
لقد قلت لك لا تترك ميا وحدها.
Why are you here eating those fruits!
لماذا أنت هنا تأكل هذه الفاكهة؟
- Miss Mia! Miss Mia, please!
- آنسة ميا! آنسة ميا، من فضلك!
Please wake up! Get up!
من فضلك استيقظ! انهض!
Miss Mia, it's already noon!
آنسة ميا، لقد حان وقت الظهر بالفعل!
- Miss Mia!
- آنسة ميا!
Happy now?
سعيدة الآن؟
Miss Mia!
آنسة ميا!
Miss Mia, can we take a selfie?
آنسة ميا، هل يمكننا التقاط صورة شخصية؟
I need pics or it didn't happen.
أحتاج إلى صور وإلا فلن يحدث ذلك.
Just to prove that you're okay.
فقط لإثبات أنك بخير.
- Thank you, Miss Mia!
- شكرا لك يا آنسة ميا!
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
Okay!
تمام!
You really left Mia alone?
هل تركت ميا وحدها حقا؟
"Leave me alone."
"اتركني وحدي."
Of course, I listened.
بالطبع استمعت.
I'm very obedient
أنا مطيع جدًا
I followed your orders, I followed hers. I listen to both of you. Now I'm here.
لقد نفّذتُ أوامركما، ونفّذتُ أوامرها. أستمع لكليكما. والآن أنا هنا.
- Right? Hey! - Argh!
- صحيح؟ هيه! - آه!
Hey, Boss V, please!
مرحبًا، يا رئيس V، من فضلك!
You know what Miss Mia's like.
أنت تعرف ما هي طبيعة السيدة ميا.
I can stay outside her house and wait there forever.
أستطيع البقاء خارج منزلها والانتظار هناك إلى الأبد.
If she doesn't want to go out, she won't.
إذا لم ترغب في الخروج، فلن تفعل.
We can't do anything about that.
لا يمكننا أن نفعل شيئا حيال ذلك.
Let's try again tomorrow, Boss V.
دعنا نحاول مرة أخرى غدًا، يا رئيس V.
What flavor was the cake you ordered that's as black as her soul?
ما هي نكهة الكعكة التي طلبتها والتي كانت سوداء مثل روحها؟
Dark chocolate.
الشوكولاتة الداكنة.
Nice, right?
جميل، أليس كذلك؟
Dark and not that sweet.
داكنة وليست حلوة إلى هذا الحد.
Dinosaur! It's a dinosaur!
ديناصور! إنه ديناصور!
I'm not a dinosaur, my name is Trexy!
أنا لست ديناصورًا، اسمي تريكسي!
A talking dinosaur!
ديناصور يتحدث!
Aah!
آه!
I won't allow it!
لن اسمح بذلك!
We have to end up together.
علينا أن ننتهي معًا.
"I have Matmat's favorite.
"لدي المفضل لدى ماتمات.
Come back here if you don't want me to break this."
"عد إلى هنا إذا كنت لا تريد مني أن أكسر هذا."
Miss, can I get a serving of vegetables?
آنسة، هل يمكنني الحصول على وجبة من الخضروات؟
I'll get this fried fish too.
سأحصل على هذه السمكة المقلية أيضًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
"THE LITTLE BROTHER KILLED HIS BIG BROTHER"
"الأخ الصغير قتل أخاه الأكبر"
"It's my birthday tomorrow.
"إنه عيد ميلادي غدًا.
Buy me a cake? Okay, any food will do".
أشتري لي كعكة؟ حسنًا، أي طعام يناسبني.
Here you go, sir.
تفضل يا سيدي.
- Thank you. - Thanks.
- شكرا لك. - شكرا.
"Fine. Forget about the birthday.
"حسنًا. انسَ عيد الميلاد.
Bring me medicine and soup. I'm sick".
"أحضر لي الدواء والحساء. أنا مريض".
I knew it. You can't resist me.
كنت أعلم ذلك. لا يمكنك مقاومتي.
So…
لذا…
What's for dinner--
ماذا يوجد في العشاء--
Aah!
آه!
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I'm sorry, ma'am.
انا آسف سيدتي.
Someone's looking for you.
شخص ما يبحث عنك.
Who?
من؟
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Patrick asked me to get their things.
لقد طلب مني باتريك أن أحضر لهم الأشياء.
So what are you?
إذن ما أنت؟
His new assistant or something?
مساعده الجديد أو شيء من هذا القبيل؟
Say whatever you want.
قل ما تريد.
I just need to get their stuff.
أنا فقط بحاجة للحصول على أغراضهم.
And you?
وأنت؟
Why are you still here?
لماذا مازلت هنا؟
I didn't get to work this morning, ma'am.
لم أذهب إلى العمل هذا الصباح، سيدتي.
I came tonight to check on some things.
لقد جئت الليلة للتحقق من بعض الأمور.
Leave.
يترك.
Hey! Why are you in there?
مهلا! لماذا أنت هناك؟
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Let's wait for her time to come.
دعونا ننتظر وقتها حتى يأتي.
That's it?
هذا كل شيء؟
I'm sorry for what I did. Please don't avoid me.
أنا آسف على ما فعلت. من فضلك لا تتجنبني.
I'm sorry for thinking about wanting you dead.
أنا آسف لأنني فكرت في رغبتي في قتلك.
You're pissing me off.
أنت تغضبني.
You're cute when you're mad.
أنت لطيف عندما تكون غاضبًا.
Why does Patrick like you?
لماذا باتريك يحبك؟
It's just us two.
إنه فقط نحن الاثنين.
Patpat is mine alone.
باتبات ملكي وحدي.
I'm all yours.
أنا لك بالكامل.